hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
Fire Style: Fire Ball Jutsu!
Wh-What is that Jutsu?!
Damn it!
Chidori!
I'll win no matter what!
Don't flatter yourself!
Stop it!
The Invisible Crack
It's a tranquil village as always...
The security sucks.
Humph!
We should just massacre everybody
in such a seedy village.
Calm down, Sakon.
We haven't come here to fight.
Shut up you chicken.
If you're scared
you should just go home
and go to bed already.
I'm telling you to calm down, Tayuya.
You understand what
our job is this time, right?
Let's go.
We escort our special guest.
Stop it!
Damn.
I can't stop completely.
Kakashi-sensei?
Naruto... That thing you just did was...
What're you guys doing
up on top of the hospital?
You went a bit too far
for just a fight you two.
That Jutsu earlier... no doubt...
Was the Rasengan.
What's going on?
How can Naruto use that Jutsu...?
Were you going to kill Naruto, Sasuke?
What're you doing giving yourself over
to a sense of superiority?
The size of the Chidori there
wasn't one to be aimed
at a comrade of the same village.
Why such infantile behavior...?
Sure enough a reunion with Itachi...
Sasuke-kun.
Damn it!
Naruto...
How far will you go...?
Kakashi-sensei...
Whatever happened to teamwork?
Was it you...
who taught him that technique?
I think Naruto is still too young
to be handling that Jutsu.
He could've killed Sasuke
had something gone wrong...
Even if it's a means of resisting
the Akatsuki
to think you would teach Naruto
that Jutsu...
Right back at you...
That Chidori was also considerably hairy.
But I didn't think he was
the kind of kid
who'd fire that Jutsu at his comrade.
Or is it that there's something quite
complicated between him and that kid?
Well all sorts.
All sorts?
Quite simply it's a relationship
like the one between you
and Orochimaru in the past.
I see.
To him, Sasuke is a comrade
and a rival at the same time...
Well, someone he considers
an equal.
Most likely he couldn't take
Sasuke's cheap provocation.
He's been chasing him...
Chasing him since the Academy days.
Are you hurt...
Scaredy Cat?
Sasuke!
I won't lose to you!
For him it's neither you
nor me now...
More than anyone...
he wants to be recognized by Sasuke.
On the other side of the coin...
Sasuke feels the speed of Naruto's growth
at close range and feels inferior.
To the extent that he thinks
he himself isn't growing at all.
Scaredy Cat?
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto has gotten strong...
And Sasuke...
I'm going to kill a certain man
no matter what.
Revenge, huh...?
I wonder if Itachi
is frustrating that kid.
So Sasuke doesn't want
to acknowledge Naruto.
If he acknowledges him
he just might deny himself
up to this point...
Rivalry is a difficult thing.
It's not a very good trend...
Maybe I'll do some scolding.
Then I leave Naruto to you.
Well, I have a mission.
And there's the Chidori thing too...
Sakura.
It's okay. Things can go back to the way
they were in the old days again.
Cheer up.
See ya.
Thanks Kakashi-sensei.
Naruto...
Sakura-chan.
Don't interfere with us!
You are weak.
Why are you weak?
It's because you don't have enough...
...hate.
What've I been doing...
up until now?
He got a nice look in those eyes.
Shall we go soon?
What do you think you're doing?
If I don't do this
you'll run away right?
You're not the type
to listen quietly to lectures.
As I recall,
that's Kakashi the Copy Ninja.
Sasuke... Forget about something
like revenge.
What?
Well, in this business
I've seen a stink of guys like you.
But the final days of those who speak
of revenge are never good.
They're tragic.
You'll only hurt yourself and
agonize more than now.
Even if you succeed in revenge
all that will remain is emptiness.
Shut up!
What do you know?
Don't talk to me as if you know!
Well calm down...
If you like
shall I go and kill the person
most important to you?
You'll be able to realize just
how far off you are
on what you just said.
Well, I wouldn't mind if you'd do that.
Unfortunately, I don't even have
one person like that.
Everyone's already been killed.
I've lived longer than you have...
The times were not good.
I know all too well
the agony of losing something.
Well, both you and I
aren't the lucky ones...
That's for damned sure.
But we're not the worst either.
You and I,
we both have already found
dear comrades, haven't we?
It's because I have lost
that I understand.
The Chidori is a power...
I gave to you because
you now have something important.
You should know that
it's not a power
to be used on your comrade
or to use for revenge
and I'm sure you know
what it should be used for.
Think hard about whether or not
what I'm saying is wrong.
It'll be tricky with a Shinobi
of that level hanging around.
So let's wait a bit.
Maybe jerks like you'd be no good.
But I could do it.
I wonder. "Two"
should be ample to rip him apart.
Don't be butting in all the time,
you idiot.
Tayuya, women shouldn't
use words like that too...
Shut up, fatso.
— More please!
Wanna head back?
Sure!
We both made it
to the top of the tree.
Sakura-chan.
I have something to talk
to you about.
I'll go out on a date with you
so come along.
Damn it...
Damn it!
The Curse Mark left by Orochimaru
during the Chunin Exam...
Kakashi-sensei said
it was okay now but...
Orochimaru-sama.
You didn't need to send out
all four members, did you?
It seems those kids are all interested
in Sasuke-kun to whom I've taken a liking.
To see what extent his power is...
A contest of strength or whatever
at this point Sasuke-kun would be
no match for them.
That is precisely why... he will come to me
in search of power.
Who're you guys?
I'm Kidomaru, the East Gate
of the Sound Ninja Four.
I'm Sakon,
the West Gate of the same.
I'm Jirobo,
the South Gate of the same.
I'm Tayuya,
the North Gate of the same.
I'm in a bad mood now...
If you wanna continue to fight here
I won't go easy on you!
GET UP aa sumimasen
get up! oh, I'm sorry
goku tama ni boku tama ni
once in a long while, once in a while
yume ni yabureru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person broken by dreams
yama no you ni mieru
kamisama ni hotokesama ni
clinging to God, clinging to Buddha
sugari naiteru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person crying
yama no you ni mieru
danran dansu de RANDEBUU
rendezvous with a happy dance circle
ore shouri no poozu da randaran
this is my victory pose, round and around
SHEIKU SHEIKU SHEIKU sagasou janai
shake shake shake let's look
owaranai baibai no RIZUMU de
with a bye-bye rhythm that never ends
yama no you ni mieru
A date, a date!
What do you want to eat, Sakura-chan?
Anything's fine.
At any rate
Kakashi-sensei's over the top.
I just wanted to fight
Sasuke a little.
But if Kakashi-sensei hadn't stopped it
right about now...
Of course which of us was stronger
would be settled.
Listen Naruto...
Next time:
"The Sound's Invitation."
I feel uneasy...